sportshero.com 2010-12-21

# SportsHero: Fantasy Premier League,Play Prediction Sports,Leagues

SportsHero.com - Privacy Policy

This policy tells you how we collect information from you on the SportsHero website (the Site), how we protect it and how we use it. SportsHero controls all personal information which you provide on the Site. SportsHero is referred to in this Privacy Policy as "we", "us", "our" and "ourselves".

What type of information we collect about you

We will collect personally identifiable information from you in a variety of ways including when you register on the Site.

Use of Cookies

We collect information through technology to make our websites more interesting and useful to you. For instance, when you come to the Site, we collect your IP address. An IP address is often associated with the portal through which you enter the Internet, like your Internet Service Provider, your company, or your university. By itself, your IP address is not personally identifiable. At times, we also use IP addresses to collect information regarding the frequency with which our guests visit various parts of our websites. We may combine this information with personally identifiable information.

Our website also uses cookies. We and other companies use cookies for a variety of purposes. For instance, when you return to one of our websites after logging in, cookies provide information to the website so that the website will remember who you are. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. If you turn cookies off, you will not have access to many features that make your Web experience smoother, like the features mentioned above, and some of our services will not function properly.

Our website uses a variety of technical methods for tracking purposes, including Web beacons. Web beacons are small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the pages of websites. We also use these technical methods to analyse the traffic patterns on our websites, such as the frequency with which our users visit various parts of our websites. These technical methods may involve the transmission of information either directly to us or to another party authorised by us to collect information on our behalf. We also use these technical methods in HTML e-mails that we send out to determine whether those e-mails have been opened and/or links within the emails have been clicked on. The information from use of these technical methods may be collected in a form that is personally identifiable.

Links to other websites

You should be aware that when you are on our websites you could be directed to other websites where the personal information collected is outside the control of SportsHero.

For example, if you click on a banner advertisement the click may take you off the Site. The privacy policy of the new website will govern the information obtained from you on such website.

Changes to this policy

We may change this policy and our terms and conditions from time to time and will post the latest version of the privacy policy on the Site. If we ever wish to use your personal information in a way which is incompatible with the information in this Privacy Policy, we will only do so with your consent.

Queries

If you have queries about our use of personal information, please send them to [contactus@sportshero.com](mailto:contactus@sportshero.com)

You can also write to us at:

Sports Hub Pvt Ltd  
Tower 2, 4th Floor,  
Vashi Infotech Park,  
Vashi Station,  
Vashi,  
Navi Mumbai - 400703.
